Guide to the Rice University President David W. Leebron Inauguration records, 2004-2006 UA 103
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Rice University President David W. Leebron Inauguration records
2004-2006
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Rice University.
UA 103
19 Linear Feet 22 boxes
Correspondence, calendars of events, event programs, invitations, agendas, mailing lists, minutes, brochures, testimonials and more related to the celebration of the 2004 inauguration of Rice University's seventh president.
Historical Sketch
For each incoming Rice president, an Inaugural Committee is formed which works with the Board of Governors and the President's Office to plan the numerous presidential welcoming events and celebrations. After the inauguration, the committee is released from duty. David W. Leebron took office as Rice University's seventh president on July 1, 2004. On Saturday, October 2, 2004, he was officially inaugurated into that post. Due to inclement weather conditions and heat and humidity, the inaugural proceedings were held at 9:30 a.m. in the Rice Gymnasium, Autry Court. The inaugural dinner was held at the Warwick Hotel. The Rice Concert Band, the Rice Chorale, the Shepherd School Brass Ensemble, and Melody Johnson, a Shepherd School soprano, provided the music for the occasion. Arthur Gottschalk, chair of composition and theory with the Shepherd School of Music, composed a special fanfare for the inauguration ceremony. More than 200 delegates representing universities and learned societies from around the world attended the inauguration, as did such distinguished guests as the consuls of Jordan, Ukraine, and Saudi Arabia; Ambassador Edward Djerejian; and Congresswoman Sheila Jackson Lee.
David Leebron was born in 1956 in Philadelphia. He earned a bachelor of art's degree (1976) and doctorate of jurisprudence (1979) from Harvard University. After college Leebron clerked at the Ninth Circuit Court of Appeals and taught at the UCLA School of Law and New York University. From 1981 to 1983, he practiced privately with the New York law firm of Cleary, Gottlieb, Steen & Hamilton. In 1989 Leebron joined the faculty of the Columbia Law School. He later became the Lucy G. Moses Professor of Law and dean of the law school, a position he remained in until his selection as Rice's president. Leebron is married to Y. Ping Sun. They have two children.
Scope and Contents
Correspondence, calendars of events, event programs, invitations, agendas, mailing lists, minutes, brochures, testimonials and more related to the celebration of the 2004 inauguration of Rice University's seventh president. The Leebron Inaugural Committee created or maintained the bulk of this material.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored offsite at the Library Service Center and require 24-hour notice for retrieval. Please contact the Woodson Research Center at 713-348-2586 or woodson@rice.edu for more information.
Restrictions on Access
This material is open for research.
Acquisition Information
This material was received from the Friends of Fondren, June 2005. The Friends of Fondren office participated extensively in the inaugural committee's work.
Related Material
Photographs connected with the inauguration of David W. Leebron are still held by the Friends of Fondren. Interested parties should contact them at: Rice University, Friends of Fondren Library – MS 245, P. O. Box 1892, Houston TX 77251-1892, or at www.rice.edu/fondren/friends.
Index Terms
Subjects
Universities and colleges; College teachers; Education
Document Types
brochures; corrrespondence; mailing lists; notes; programs (documents)
Subjects (Persons)
Leebron, David W., 1956-
- Series I: Inaugural Committee Documents, 241208
  Scope and Contents note
  Series I is made up of the inaugural committee's working papers. This material consists of committee lists; faculty, institutional, foundation, and dignitary mailing lists; meetings and agendas; thank you notes; the inauguration schedule; and information related to the 1993 inauguration of Rice's sixth president, S. Malcolm Gillis. There is limited correspondence. This series is organized alphabetically.
  - Administrative Set-up, Notebook ID, 241245 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 241244 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Envelopes, 241243 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Exhibit, 241242 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Gillis Inauguration, 241241 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Inauguration Matrix, 241240 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Leebron Schedule, 241239 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Letterhead, 241238 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Meeting Agendas, 241237 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Minutes, 241236 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence, 241235 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Mission Statement, 241234 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Music, 241233 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Nametags, 241232 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Planning, 241231 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Roster, 241230 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Schedule, 241229 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Thank you notes, 241228 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Wrap-up, 241227 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Mailing List – U.S. Institutions, 241226 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Mailing List – Administrative Officers, 241225 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Mailing List – City Council, 241224 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Mailing List – Consuls, 241223 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Mailing List – Corporations, 241222 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Mailing List – Faculty, 241221 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Mailing Lists – Faculty Emeriti, 241220 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Mailing Lists – Foundations, 241219 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Mailing Lists – International Institutions, 241218 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Mailing Lists – Learned Societies and Associations, 241217 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Mailing Lists – Leebron Guests, 241216 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Mailing Lists – miscellaneous, 241215 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Mailing Lists – Rice Associates, 241214 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Mailing List – Shadyside, 241213 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Mailing List – Staff Retirees, 241212 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Mailing List – VIP, 241211 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Mailing List - Staff, 241210 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Printing – Invoice Copies with Samples, 241209 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Series II: Investiture/Delegates, 241179
  Series II includes investiture invitations; investiture programs; investiture tickets; and internal documents related to digital recording of inaugural events, a timeline of inaugural events, transportation, parking, line of procession, regalia, and the presidential medal. Series II also includes information about the delegates who were invited to or who attended the inaugural events. Delegate lists are provided both numerically by the founding date and alphabetically by the name of the institution or society. This series also includes other types of information provided for delegates, such as a schedule of events, details about transportation, Houston events, and robing. This series is arranged alphabetically.
  - Investiture Invitation – Delegates, 241207 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Investiture Invitation – Faculty/Rice Associates, 241206 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Investiture Invitation – Staff, 241205 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Investiture Invitation – Students, 241204 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Investiture – AV, 241203 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Investiture – Disabilities, 241202 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Investiture – Facilities and Engineering, 241201 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Investiture – Inclement Weather Plan, 241200 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Investiture – Invocation, 241199 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Investiture – Logistics – Sun/Weather, 241198 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Investiture – Order of Marching, 241197 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Investiture – Parking Passes, 241196 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Investiture – Presidential Medal, 241195 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Investiture – Programs, 241194 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Investiture – Regalia, 241193 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Investiture – Delegate Packets, 241192 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Investiture – Scenario, 241191 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Investiture summons (5 copies, 1 signed by E. William Barnett, Chair, Board of Trustees), 241190 (Box OV, Folder -)
  - Investiture – Tickets, 241189 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Investiture – Transportation, 241188 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Delegates – Attendees, 241187 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Delegates – Chairman's Letter, 241186 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Delegates – Hotel Card, 241185 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Delegates – Houston events, 241184 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Delegates – Rice News, 241183 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Delegates – Robing/Transportation, 241182 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Delegates – Schedule of Events, 241181 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Delegates - Tickets, 241180 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Series III: Events, 241152
  Series III is made up of events connected with the inauguration of David W. Leebron. It is arranged chronologically. Events covered include an art exhibit, cocktail reception, alumni/student reception, inaugural concert, and post-investiture luncheon and dinner.
  - Save-the-date Cards, 241178 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Summons – Invitation, 241177 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Art Exhibit, 241176 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Staff Reception – Invitation, 241175 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Staff Reception – Venue/Menu, 241174 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Friday Cocktail Reception – Event Plan, 241173 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Friday Cocktail Reception – Invitation, 241172 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Friday - President's Inaugural Concert (CD), 241171 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Alumni/Student Reception Invitation for Alumni, 241170 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Alumni/Student Reception Invitation for Students, 241169 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Alumni/Student Reception – Plan, 241168 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Multi-event Response Card, 241167 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Saturday Luncheon – Invitations, 241166 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Saturday Luncheon - Speakers, 241165 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Saturday Luncheon – Response Card/Envelope, 241164 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Luncheon – Venue/Menu, 241163 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Saturday Dinner – Guest Lists, 241162 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Saturday Dinner – Foundation List, 241161 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Saturday Dinner – Invitation, 241160 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Saturday Dinner – Response Cards, 241159 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Saturday Dinner – Table Cards, 241158 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Saturday Dinner – Venue, 241157 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Sunday Brunch – Invitations, 241156 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - RSVP – Delegates, 241155 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - RSVP – Faculty/Rice Associates, 241154 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Warwick Hotel Guests, 241153 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Series IV: Expenses, Printing, Media/Publicity, 241132
  Series IV contains a list of inaugural expenses incurred and is arranged alphabetically. This includes expenses related to the investiture itself, as well as those related to printing, publicity, events, and administration. A media plan, copies of printed materials such as the Leebron Family insert and a visitor's guide that went into each delegate's package, and a typescript of a commemorative book about Rice and the inaugural are also within this series.
  - Expenses – Administrative; Administrative Documents: Labor, Office,Office Supplies,Telephone, 241151 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Expenses – Events: Staff Reception, Friday Cocktail Reception, Alumni/Student Reception, Saturday Luncheon, Saturday Dinner, 241150 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Expenses – Investiture Related: Facilities and Engineering, Investiture, Medal/Scroll, Memory Books, Regalia, Security/EMS, Transportation, 241149 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Expenses – Multimedia Services, 241148 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Expenses – Music, 241147 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Expenses – Postage, 241146 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Expenses – Printing, 241145 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Printing – Commemorative Book, 241144 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Printing – Estimates, 241143 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Printing – Nametags, 241142 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Printing – Leebron Family Insert, 241141 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Printing – Packing Lists, 241140 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Printing – Proofs, 241139 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Printing – Schedules, 241138 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Printing – Scroll, 241137 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Printing – Visitors Guide, 241136 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Media Plan, 241135 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Website, 241134 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Publicity, 241133 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Series V: Testimonials (Boxes 6-10), 240896
  - Agnes Scott College, 241131 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Alfred University, 241130 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Amberton University, 241129 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Appalachian State University, 241128 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Appalachian State University, 241127 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Arkansas State University Augustana College, 241126 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Augustana College, 241125 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Austin College, 241124 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Auxiliary Bishop of Galveston-Houston, 241123 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Babson College, 241122 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Baylor University, 241121 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Beloit College, 241120 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Bennington College, 241119 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Berry College, 241118 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Boise State University, 241117 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Brandeis University, 241116 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Brigham Young University, 241115 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - California Polytechnic State University, 241114 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - California State University, Dominguez Hills, 241113 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - California State University, Los Angeles, 241112 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - California State University, Northridge, 241111 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - California State University, Stanislaus, 241110 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Centre College, 241109 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - City of Houston, TX, Ada Edwards, 241108 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Claremont Graduate University, 241107 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Claremont McKenna College, 241106 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Clark University, 241105 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Clark Atlanta University, 241104 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Clemson University, 241103 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Colgate University, 241102 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - College of Santa Fe, 241101 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - College of Staten Island of the City University of New York, 241100 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - College of William & Mary, 241099 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - College of Wooster, 241098 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Colorado State University, 241097 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Columbia University, 241096 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Connecticut College, 241095 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Consulate General of the People's Republic of China, 241094 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Consulate of Australia, 241093 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Dartmouth College, 241092 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Davidson College, 241091 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Denison University, 241090 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - DePauw University, 241089 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Dickinson College, 241088 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Emory University, 241087 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Emporia State University, 241086 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Episcopal Theological Seminary of the Southwest, 241085 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Fairleigh Dickinson University, 241084 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Florida International University, 241083 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Follett Higher Education Group, 241082 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Franklin & Marshall College, 241081 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Gakushuin University, 241080 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Gallaudet University, 241079 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Goucher College, 241078 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Grambling State University, 241077 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Gustavus Adolphus College, 241076 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Hampden-Sydney College, 241075 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Harris County Commissioner Precinct 1, 241074 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Harvard College, 241073 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Hendrix College, 241072 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Hope College, 241071 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Idaho State University, 241070 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Illinois Wesleyan University, 241069 (Box 6, Folder -)
  - Indiana University, 241068 (Box 7, Folder -)
  - Indiana State University, 241067 (Box 7, Folder -)
  - Iowa State University, 241066 (Box 7, Folder -)
  - James Madison University, 241065 (Box 7, Folder -)
  - John Marshall Law School, 241064 (Box 7, Folder -)
  - Kingdom of Saudi Arabia Ministry of Higher Education, 241063 (Box 7, Folder -)
  - Knox College, 241062 (Box 7, Folder -)
  - Kyoto University, 241061 (Box 7, Folder -)
  - Lake Forest College, 241060 (Box 7, Folder -)
  - LaSalle University, 241059 (Box 7, Folder -)
  - Lehman College, 241058 (Box 7, Folder -)
  - LeTourneau University, 241057 (Box 7, Folder -)
  - Lewis & Clark College, 241056 (Box 7, Folder -)
  - Loras College, 241055 (Box 7, Folder -)
  - Loyola College in Maryland, 241054 (Box 7, Folder -)
  - Lubbock Christian University, 241053 (Box 7, Folder -)
  - Macalester College, 241052 (Box 7, Folder -)
  - Marietta College, 241051 (Box 7, Folder -)
  - McDaniel College, 241050 (Box 7, Folder -)
  - McMurry University, 241049 (Box 7, Folder -)
  - Mercer University, 241048 (Box 7, Folder -)
  - Meredith College, 241047 (Box 7, Folder -)
  - Middlebury College, 241046 (Box 7, Folder -)
  - Millersville University, 241045 (Box 7, Folder -)
  - Mills College, 241044 (Box 7, Folder -)
  - Millsaps College, 241043 (Box 7, Folder -)
  - Mississippi State University, 241042 (Box 7, Folder -)
  - Montana State University, 241041 (Box 7, Folder -)
  - Muhlenberg College, 241040 (Box 7, Folder -)
  - Nagoya University, 241039 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - National Academy of Engineering, 241038 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - National Taiwan University, 241037 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Nebraska Wesleyan University, 241036 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - New York Institute of Technology, 241035 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Northern Illinois University, 241034 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Northwestern University, 241033 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Ohio State University, 241032 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Old Dominion University, 241031 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Oswego State University of New York, 241030 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Paul Quinn College, 241029 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Peace College, 241028 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Pepperdine University, 241027 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Pitzer College, 241026 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Pomona College, 241025 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Pratt Institute, 241024 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Princeton University, 241023 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Providence College, 241022 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Queen's University at Kingston, 241021 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Queen's University, Belfast, 241020 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Randolph-Macon College, 241019 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Randolph-Macon Woman's College, 241018 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Ripon College, 241017 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Roanoke College, 241016 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Rollins College, 241015 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Roosevelt University, 241014 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Royal Society, 241013 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Rutgers State University of New Jersey, 241012 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Salve Regina University, 241011 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - San Diego State University, 241010 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Santa Clara University, 241009 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Scripps Women's College, 241008 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Seattle Pacific University, 241007 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Senate of the State of Texas, 241006 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Silesian University of Technology, 241005 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Simpson University, 241004 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Skidmore College, 241003 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Slippery Rock University of Pennsylvania, 241002 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Smith College, 241001 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Southern California Institute of Architecture, 241000 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Southwestern Adventist University, 240999 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Southwestern University, 240998 (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Springfield College, 240997 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - St. John's College, 240996 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - Saint John's University, 240995 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - St. Mary's College of Maryland, 240994 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - St. Olaf College, 240993 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - State of Texas House of Representatives, 240992 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - State University of New York, Buffalo, 240991 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - State University of New York, Cortland, 240990 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - State University of New York, Fredonia, 240989 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - State University of New York, Old Westbury, 240988 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - State University of New York, Potsdam, 240987 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - Stephens College, 240986 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - Stetson University, 240985 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - Swedish Academy, 240984 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - Tecnologico de Monterrey, 240983 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - Temple University, 240982 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - Texas A&M University, Kingsville, 240981 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - Texas Christian University, 240980 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - Texas Southern University, 240979 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - Texas State University, 240978 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - Texas Tech University System, 240977 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - Texas Woman's University, 240976 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - Towson University, 240975 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - Trinity College, Cambridge, 240974 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - Truman State University, 240973 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - Tufts University, 240972 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - Tulane University, 240971 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - United Nations Secretary-General, 240970 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - Universidad de Salamanca, 240969 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - Universitas Indonesia, 240968 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, 240967 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - University College London, 240966 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - University of California, Davis, 240965 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - University of California, Irvine, 240964 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - University of California, Los Angeles, 240963 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - University of Cape Town, 240962 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - University of Central Arkansas, 240961 (Box 4, Folder -)
  - University of Chicago, 240960 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - University of Cincinnati, 240959 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - University of Crete, 240958 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - University of Dayton, 240957 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - University of Edinburgh, 240956 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - University of Georgia, 240955 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - University of Hawaii at Manoa, 240954 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - University of Houston [see oversize], 240953 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - University of Houston System, 240952 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - University of Illinois, 240951 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - University of Iowa, 240950 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - University of Kansas, 240949 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - University of Kentucky, 240948 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - University of Maine, 240947 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - University of Mary Hardin-Baylor, 240946 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - University of Maryland, 240945 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - University of Maryland, Baltimore County, 240944 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - University of Massachusetts, Amherst, 240943 (Box 9, Folder -)
  - University of Michigan, 240942 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - University of Minnesota, 240941 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - University of Montana, 240940 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - University of Monterrey, 240939 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - University of Montreal [see oversize], 240938 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - University of Munich, 240937 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - University of New Mexico, 240936 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - University of North Dakota, 240935 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - University of Notre Dame, 240934 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - University of Oregon, 240933 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - University of Pennsylvania, 240932 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - University of Pennsylvania Law School, 240931 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - University of Pittsburgh, 240930 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - University of Rhode Island, 240929 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - University of Richmond, 240928 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - University of South Alabama, 240927 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - University of South Dakota, 240926 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - University of South Florida, 240925 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - University of St. Thomas, 240924 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - University of Texas at Tyler, 240923 (Box 10, Folder -)